《非常人贩3》
Ninety-one，Ninety-two…
九十一 九十二
It's down there。Where？If they catch us…
在那儿 哪儿？如果被他们发现了…
There's a million bottles of booze in there.
这儿的酒有上百万瓶
You think they're gonna miss one？
你觉得他们会知道少了一瓶么？
Weather is with us，sir.
天气不错 先生
We arrive in port in a couple of hours.
我们将在几小时后到达港口
Very good.
干得不错
You're welcome，sir.
谢谢夸奖 先生
Man，I never smelt anything like this。Not even when you're in the crapper.
伙计 这种味道我从没闻到过 即使厕所的味道也比这好闻
Oh，what，your shit smells like roses？
你的大便什么时候好闻过？
Hey，look.
嘿 看
I'll give you a hand.
我来帮你
Thought you said it was booze。That's what the papers said.
记得你说运的是酒啊 文件上是这么写的
Captain，we have a breach in lower level。Look.
船长 船舱底层有情况 快看
Which section？101.
哪个区？101
Fuck。Take the wheel.
操 你来掌舵
Yes，sir。Fuck.
是 先生 操
Close the door！Get the masks.
关门！戴上防毒面具
Holy shit.
天呐
Take care of them.
快处理掉
Morning。Passport，please.
早上好 请出示护照
Rough seas？
浪很大？
The sea was smooth。The party was a bit rough，if you know what I mean.
还可以 只是派对上海过头了 你懂的吧
Ibiza。Yeah.
伊比沙岛 是的
Thanks.
谢谢
When I was a kid，my father used to take me fishing.
小时候 父亲常带我去钓鱼
Never could figure out how he knew where the fish were.
但我一直不明白 他怎么知道哪儿有鱼
They were always exactly where he said they would be.
他总是准确无误
Security check.
安全检查
Do I look like a security risk？
我看起来像危险分子吗？
Please step out of the car and bring your documents to the office.
请下车 带上你的证件去办公室
My documents are right here，sir.
证件就在这儿 警官
The computer is in the office.
但计算机在办公室
Her too.
带上她
She's sleeping.
她在睡觉
With her documents。Okay，sure.
还有她的证件 好的 没问题
什么鬼东西？
Come on。You're gonna lose it.
快 它要跑了
Close，inspector，you're close.
快了 警长 快钓上来了
That's a big one。Go left，go left.
是条大的 向左 向左
Don't let him get away.
别让它跑了
You're close.
快钓上来了
Go left，go left！Go right！
向左 左边！向右！
Must be Moby Dick you hooked。Need some help？
肯定钓到了条白鲸 需要帮忙吗？
No，thank you，Frank.
不 谢谢 Frank
I have been fishing these waters since before you were born.
我在这片儿钓鱼的时候 你还没出世呢
You were close，inspector。You were close.
快了 警长 快钓上来了
Good thing that we French have such a highly developed sense of humor.
幸运的是 我们法国人皆具幽默感
With all due respect，the French think Jerry Lewis is a genius.
恕我直言 法国人认为Jerry Lewis是个天才
- Jerry Lewis is a genius。- Dean was the genius.
- Jerry Lewis的确是个天才啊 - Dean才是天才
No，Dean just stood there with a drink and a cigarette.
不 Dean只是拿著酒和香烟站在那里
My point exactly。Anyone can fall down and get a laugh.
但关键是他可以让所有人都捧腹大笑
How many people can do it standing still with a drink and a cigarette？
有多少人可以拿著酒和香烟站在那 能做到这样？
喂？
喂 我是Tarconi
好的
I am afraid our day of leisure is cut short.
恐怕我们的悠闲日子得提前结束了
There is a big mess in Marseilles.
马赛那边出了点儿麻烦
Some madman driving an Audi at impossible speeds.
一个疯子驾著奥迪横冲直撞
Don't look at me.
别那样看著我
That is the first place the chief told me to look.
长官让我注意观察第一反应
But I will tell him you have the perfect alibi.
但我会告诉他 你有完美的不在场证据
As usual.
像往常一样
Tarconi！
Tarconi啊
Please！I am sorry，Frank.
帮帮忙！对不起 Frank
It's our first bite！Yeah，yeah.
这可是第一次上钩！是啊 没错
Please。Yeah.
拜托 好啊
Stop the boat。Come on.
停船 拜托
No。No，Frank。Come on，please.
不 不行 Frank 别这样 拜托
Purpose of your visit，Mr。Johnson？
Johnson先生 您此行的目的？
Business.
生意
What kind of business？
什么生意？
Environmental protection.
环境保护
Thank you.
谢谢
Mr。Minister，you're giving the opening address at an EU conference…
部长先生 明天欧盟会议的开幕致词中 您将说到…
on environmental impact of industry in Odessa tomorrow.
工业对敖德萨环境的影响
What is top on your list of priorities？It's a short list.
关键内容是什么呢？很简单
There's only one item：The environment and how to protect it.
只有一项：环境 以及如何保护它
In the face of increasing pressure…
在这个经济全球化的时代…
for industries to compete successfully in a global economy…
工业竞争取得成功的压力越来越大…
that goal can sometimes come up against some very harsh realities.
不可否认 目标有时会和残酷的现实相冲突…
Well，not as harsh as a polluted and uninhabitable planet.
但是 更为残酷的是一个污染和不适于居住的地球
Gentlemen，if you'll excuse me now…
先生们 请原谅…
I have trees to save and industrialists to disappoint.
我得去拯救树木 让工业家们扫兴了
Your speech for tomorrow。Any good？
您明天的演讲稿 你觉得如何？
It's going to piss off a lot of people。Excellent.
将会令很多人生气 非常好
Hello？
喂？
Mr。Minister？
部长先生吗？
Who is this？
你是谁？
My name is not important.
我是谁并不重要
I've been put in charge of the negotiations…
您插手的 关于…
you are engaged in with Ecocorp…
Eco公司在乌克兰经营许可…
for issuance of their license to do business in the Ukraine.
是由我负责谈判的
You must be misinformed，Mr。Whatever-Your-Name-Is.
不管你是谁 你肯定是弄错了
I've terminated negotiations permanently.
我已经永久性终止谈判
I think you will reconsider that position…
如果您看过信封里面的文件…
once you have a chance to study the documents in the envelope.
我认为您会重新考虑的
I'll be in touch.
好好考虑下吧
Yeah，there's been an accident.
喂 这里发生了事故
Send an ambulance，8 Route de la Falaise.
地址是德拉萨佛雷斯路8号 请派救护车来
Malcolm.
Malcolm啊
Malcolm。Malcolm.
Malcolm Malcolm啊
I asked you for your price。What is this？
我是问你的要价 这是什么？
A man who might be interested in taking the job。This man will.
一个可能会对这个活儿感兴趣的人
My boss said you're the man for the job.
我老板说 你是最适合的人选
Your boss got his facts wrong.
你老板搞错了
Two things you should know about my boss：
关于我老板 你应当知道两件事：
He never gets his facts wrong，he never takes no for an answer.
他从不出错 他从不接受拒绝
Well，there's a first time for everything.
凡事都有第一次
Well，not this time.
但不是这一次
You don't wanna do this.
你不会想这样做的
I don't think you're in a position to tell me what I do and don't wanna do.
你没资格告诉我该做什么 不该做什么
You have 10 seconds to change your mind.
给你10秒钟改变主意
I'll give you five seconds to remove your hand.
给你5秒钟 拿开你的手
Malcolm。Malcolm.
Malcolm Malcolm啊
You hear me？
听得到我说话吗？
Mal，I said drop in anytime，but I didn't mean…
Mal 我是说过 你任何时候来 我都欢迎 但不是表示…
Nowhere else to go。Just take it easy，okay？
我无处可去了 放松点儿 好吗？
Don't move me from the car.
别弄我出来
It's just get you comfortable till the ambulance arrives。No ambulance.
只是想在救护车来之前 让你舒服点 不需要救护车
You need a doctor，you've been shot。I can't take care of this.
你需要去看医生 你中枪了 我处理不了这个
Not far from car.
不能离开车
Relax.
放松
Just try to stay calm。We'll have you fixed up in no time.
保持冷静 你会没事儿的
He's inside。Quick，it's serious.
他在里面 快 伤势很严重
这边么？
Sir？
先生？
You wanna be careful moving him。We know our job，okay？
移动他时你要小心 用不著你来教 好吗？
Sir，can you hear me？
先生 能听到我说话吗？
This car No…
这辆车不…
If you hear me，press my hand.
如果你能听到 按一下我的手
The car…
这辆车…
慢点儿 小心
快到了
Am I in heaven？
我在天堂吗？
Actually，you're in a bit of the shit.
事实上 你在地狱
You'll help me out of it？
你会帮助我走出地狱吗？
That depends on how deep you're in.
这要看你陷得有多深了
Don't trust anyone。Couldn't agree with you more.
不要相信任何人 绝对同意
Come on。No！Don't leave the car！
来吧 不！不能离开车！
What's so special about the car？Not the car.
这车有这么特别么？跟车没关系
Wait！
等等！
I told you.
我告诉过你
Don't trust anyone.
不要相信任何人
I told you.
我告诉过你
I took the liberty of bringing your suit.
我冒昧给你拿了套衣服来
It's what you wear when you're working，correct？
这是你工作时的穿著 没错吧？
Correct。But I'm not working.
没错 但我不是在工作
You see，boss？I told you。Please，Joseph.
看吧 老板？我告诉过你了 拜托 Joseph
Your approach was not very effective in presenting our proposal the first time.
是你在表达我们意愿时 没有用对方法吧
Thank you.
谢谢
As I was saying…
就像我说的…
we came to you in good faith。You said you were unavailable.
我们很有诚意去见你 而你却说你做不到
We contracted with the man whose number you gave us.
只给了我们一个电话号码 我们与电话上的人签了约
He proved to be ineffective.
事实证明 他无法胜任
And now I am left with unfinished business.
现在我的生意还没完成
The way I see it，you're responsible.
在我看来 这是你的责任
I understand your point of view.
我明白你的想法
But I'm still unavailable.
但我还是做不到
Boss，can I say something？
老板 我能说一句么？
Anyone else wanna say something？
还有谁想说话么？
Good.
很好
Find me a smarter one.
给我找一个更聪明的
You have three seconds to change your mind…
给你三秒钟改变主意…
or you're gonna be permanently unavailable.
否则你永远也别想改了
One.
一
Two.
二
One condition.
有个条件
I'm listening.
说吧
I drive my own car.
我要开我自己的车
Deal.
成交
In anticipation of your answer，we took the liberty of bringing your car.
你的回答早就在意料之中了 所以我们冒昧把你的车也开来了
Changed the oil，gave it a tune-up，took out all the non-essential material.
换了油 优化了发动机 拿出了所有不必要的零件
Left the switch-over license plates。Love that.
更换了牌照 爱死它了
Replaced the GPS with one of our own.
装上了我们的全球定位系统
Preprogrammed。More efficient that way.
安装了既定程序的 这样会更有效率
Why I was so insistent on using only the best man for this assignment？
为什么我要这么坚持 用最适合的人来完成这项任务呢？
We're playing in a much larger game here.
我们在玩一个更大的游戏
Don't think of this as just another job。Think of it as a mission.
不要以为这只是随便的一份工作 把它当成任务来完成
I'm so pleased to find we share the same approach to our work.
我很高兴地发现 在对待工作上 我们有很多共同点
I make a deal，that's the deal。Just like you.
我答应了就会做到 你也一样
You don't like names。Neither do I。We're both precise.
你不喜欢问名字 我也是 我们都很谨慎
Neither one of us has any interest in what we're paid to do…
报酬以外的事情 我们都没有任何兴趣…
beyond what we are paid to do。Those are your rules，right？
那些是你的规则 没错吧？
You forgot one.
你忘了一点
I work alone。I thought you might like the company.
我一个人干 我以为你可能会喜欢有个人作伴
Thought you wanted me to complete a mission.
我还以为你想要我完成任务
You're right。I do.
没错 的确想
Wait.
等等
What，you wanna change the rules？
什么 你想改变规则？
Every rule has an exception。Let's make one for today.
每个规则皆有例外 今天就破例下吧
You're the boss.
你说了算
Anything else？
没问题了吧？
The jewelry。Anything I should know？
那个手镯 有什么你该告诉我的么？
You remember those jokers trying to blow up airliners…
你记得那些小丑通过了安全检查 在飞机上却能把液体制成炸弹…
by sneaking liquids through and combining them onboard？
想炸毁客机的事儿吧？
Same principle，just refined.
原理相同 只是这个更精制
Twenty-five feet from the car…
离车25英尺…
yellow light comes on，signaling the first liquid is ready.
黄灯亮 那是第一管液体已经准备好的信号
Fifty feet，orange.
五十英尺 橙色
Second liquid flows into the chamber.
第二管液体准备就绪
Seventy-five feet，you're gonna see red.
75英尺 你将会看到红色
Time to go.
你们该走了
This phone is programmed to call only one number，mine.
这部电话只设置了我的号码
When you pass the first toll on the road going north，call me，all right？
过了向北的第一个收费站 打给我 没问题吧？
Money for gas and food.
汽油和食物的钱
Any other questions？
还有问题吗？
Would you mind buckling your seat belt？
系上安全带好吗？
Don't suppose you wanna tell me what this is all about？
难道你不该告诉我 这一切究竟是怎么回事儿么？
Great.
好极了
Ocean Pearl requesting cargo clearance.
海洋珍珠号请求货物清关
The papers are with the environmental agency.
文件已送达环境署
Drop anchor and wait to dock.
抛下锚 在码头等候
We'll inform you when they're signed。Okay.
他们一签署 我们就通知你们 好的
I know what happened to you.
我知道你是怎么回事儿
But what happened to Frank？
但Frank是怎么回事儿呢？
Colonel Medved over at Intelligence has been given all the information.
情报局的Medved上校已经收到所有的信息
He knows it's top priority.
他知道那是头等大事
He wants you to know he has his best men on it.
他想要您知道 他会派最得力的人负责
He'll keep it out of official channels.
他会避开官方渠道
He suggests you buy as much time as you can.
他建议您尽可能多的争取时间
警长
车能拖去实验室吗？
告诉他们开始吧 这儿完了我就过去
他说开工
操！
移开！
警察在办公！
Look，I don't know what your part in all this is or isn't。And I don't really care.
听著 我不知道你在这事上扮演什么角色 我也不关心
You were here first，you know more than I do…
你先加入 知道的比我多…
download me on what you know.
把你所知道的 都告诉我
I know nothing.
我一无所知
How did you know Malcolm？
你怎么认识Malcolm的？
I didn't.
我不认识
You just happened to end up in a car with a man you don't know？
你差点就跟他一起死在车里了 还不认识？
I'm now in a car with man I don't know.
我现在也跟一个不认识的男人坐在车里
Aren't you supposed to make a call？
你不是该打电话的吗？
Nice to hear from you.
很高兴接到你电话
You can skip the pleasantries。Just give me the code.
客套话就省省吧 给我密码
1-1-2-6.
是1-1-2-6
Call me when you arrive.
到了再打给我
What's in Budapest？
布达佩斯那儿有什么？
Goulash。Beer.
匈牙利肉汤 啤酒
All right.
很好
Let's rewind here，start with the proper introductions.
我们重新来过 从正式介绍开始
What happened to the rule of no names？
你办事儿不是从不问姓名的么？
I'm suspending that rule for the moment.
那条规则暂时放一边
I'm Frank Martin.
我叫Frank Martin
And your name is？
那你叫？
What matters，my name？
我叫什么有关系么？
Well，we're in this situation together.
我们现在同在一条船上
No.
不是
We're sitting here with two exploding bracelets on，going to the same place.
我们俩 带著两个都会爆炸的手镯坐在这儿 目的地相同
I'd call that being in the same situation.
这就叫同坐一条船
It's not。They are going to kill you.
错 他们会杀了你的
I'm aware of that.
我知道
In all probability，after they kill me，you're next on the list.
十之八九 他们杀了我之后 你就是下一个
Now，if I'm gonna keep that from happening，I'm gonna need a little help.
现在 如果要阻止这一切发生 我需要一点帮助
From the top。We have this problem.
首先 我们有个问题
You think I don't know it's a problem？
你以为我不知道有问题么？
I look stupid to you？
在你看来 我很蠢？
I didn't say you were stupid.
我没有说过你蠢
But we have a problem
但是我们的确存在一个问题
and you're not being very helpful in participating in the solution of it.
不过要解决的话 你也帮不上什么忙
I don't want to talk anymore.
我不想再说下去了
Fine.
好吧
What did you say your name was？
你刚说你叫什么来著？
Frank。Frank Martin.
Frank 叫Frank Martin
Frank Martin.
Frank Martin啊
Valentina.
Valentina啊
Pleased to meet you.
很高兴见到你
警长 GPS系统已经被拆掉了 警长？没错 GPS系统已经被拿走了
The gentlemen from Ecocorp are here.
Ecocorp公司的人到了
Show them in.
让他们进来
Gentlemen.
你们好
Mr。Minister.
部长先生
We'd like to thank you for reconsidering our proposal
很感谢您在匆忙
on such short notice。You make it very hard not to.
重新考虑我们的建议 想不考虑都难
Well，yes。We do have a reputation of not taking no for an answer.
嗯 对 我们从不接受拒绝
Here are the contracts.
这些是合约
All in order.
都准备好了
We were told the ships couldn't be cleared
我们曾被告知 除非得到您的亲笔签字
unless you personally signed off on them.
否则船队不能清关
Ships？
船队？
I thought there was only one.
我以为只有一只
Oh，well，here's the thing.
噢 好的 是这样的
In order to make the venture more profitable
为了使这次冒险更具价值
we need to process the material in a volume that makes sense.
我们需要增加份量 这样才会更有意义
How many ships are we talking about？
所说的船 到底有多少只？
Plus the one in the port waiting on clearance，eight.
加上在港口等待清关的 共八只
Eight.
八只
This year.
今年
Protecting the environment is a long-term commitment.
保护环境并不能立竿见影
You've said so yourself，haven't you？
你自己说的 没错吧？
And I will do again tomorrow in Odessa
我明天在敖德萨同样会说
where I will sign these.
这些东西到了那儿再签吧
We were really hoping to settle this today.
我们真心希望今天就能解决这事儿
I want to review them，now that there are some addendums.
我想再仔细看看 后面还有些附录
Twenty-four hours doesn't make a difference
对这种长期承诺来说
on such a long-term commitment，will it？
多二十四小时有何不同呢？
No，of course not.
好吧 当然不会
Then I will see you tomorrow in Odessa。Let's say 9 a.m.
那么 明天敖德萨见 早上9点
Yes.
好的
Okay，I'll stay.
好的 我等著
But the material is leaking everywhere。And？
但是原料正在四处泄漏 然后呢？
We won't be able to hide it。I'll take care of it，just give me some time.
我们隐瞒不下去了 我会处理的 再给我多点时间
If ever they check…
要是他们查起来…
Easy。The deal will be closed very soon.
别紧张 交易很快就会达成的
Twenty-four hours。No more.
二十四小时 不能再拖了
Yes？I've bought you another 24 hours.
喂？我为你们再争取了24小时
You have until tomorrow，9 a.m.
到明天早上9点
That should be more than enough time.
时间绰绰有余
Do you have a lead？
有头绪了吗？
Better than a lead.
不止是有头绪
A location.
我们拿到了一台定位器
警长
国际刑警拿过来的片子
是通往罗多尔夫
联系我们的德国朋友们
是 可是我要说什么呢？
让他们期待与我共进晚餐吧
I'm hungry.
我饿了
We're 100 kilometers from beer and sausage.
我们离啤酒和香肠还有100公里远
I don't like sausage.
我不喜欢香肠
What would you like？
那你喜欢什么？
Veal.
小牛肉
Roast，with carrots…
烤过的 和上胡萝卜…
and beets.
还有甜菜一起
In gravy，with Madeira in stock.
加些汤汁 配上马德拉产的白葡萄酒
Nothing to start？
不来个前菜？
A salad.
一份沙拉
Greens tossed with balsamic.
用从摩地纳运来的意大利黑醋
From Modena.
拌的青菜
Aged？
腌制的？
Of course，aged.
当然 腌过的
And for dessert？
那甜点呢？
Sachertorte.
萨赫蛋糕
With whipped cream or without？
要抹生奶油吗？
With.
当然
To drink？
喝的呢？
Wine.
葡萄酒
Tokaj，perhaps？
或许 托卡葡萄酒？
Ice wine.
加冰么
Of course.
当然
（方向错误）
What are you doing？Seeing a man about some jewelry.
你在干什么？去见一个对首饰很在行的人
（偏离路线）
He's gone off the reservation.
他走错了道
Send someone to get him back on.
派人去教教他该怎么走
Don't kill him.
别杀他
Frank。It's so good to see you，mein Freund.
Frank 见到你太好了 朋友
Good to see you too，Otto.
我也很高兴见到你 Otto
You didn't mention you bring company.
怎么没跟我说还带了女朋友来的啊
It's not really company.
不是女朋友
It's…
那个…
complicated.
有点复杂
With you，it's always complicated。But you can tell me about it…
跟著你 有什么会不复杂的
over a nice schnitzel with Kartoffelsalat I have prepared.
我准备了一份美味的炸猪排和土豆色拉 我们可以边吃边谈…
Hey，Otto，you know I love your schnitzel
嘿 Otto 你知道我爱吃你做的炸猪排
but we need to get rid of this first.
但是我们首先得摆脱这个
Binary free-form magnetic-resolution technology.
二元自由形式磁性分解技术
English，please，Otto.
说英语 拜托 Otto
There's a program the Pentagon has funded
五角大楼通过他们的一家附属公司
through one of their subsidiary front companies
出资赞助了一个
that's been experimenting with this new kind of weaponry
基于磁引力理论的
based on the theory of magnetic attraction.
研发新型武器的项目
Very hush-hush stuff.
这是极度机密的事情
I didn't realize you were in the loop on the Pentagon hush-hush.
我可不知道你在五角大楼的极度机密的消息圈内
You wouldn't believe what you can discover
当你任由你的手指在互联网上漫步时
when you left your fingers walking through the Internet.
你所发现的东西 会让你觉得难以置信
You wanna see the invasion plans for Iran？
你想看看入侵伊朗的计划书吗？
Maybe some other time.
下次吧
Right now we need to get this thing off without blowing myself to Iran.
现在 我们得把这玩意儿弄下来 不然被轰到伊朗去的就是我了
I don't wanna bother you with the details
我不想拿细节来烦你
but usually there's a transmitter plate close by.
但是 通常都会有个发射器在附近的
You should not be doing this.
你不必这样做
First you don't talk，now you offer advice.
之前你不想说 现在你又来劝告
Not advice。A warning.
不是劝告 是警告
Well，a little late for warnings，don't you think？
噢 你不认为警告来得有点迟了吗？
I agree with you.
我同意你
You're off course.
你偏离路线了
Should I？Yeah，you should.
我继续吗？没错 继续
Look，fellas
听著 伙计们
some things in the car were a bit off，needed checking.
车子有点小问题 需要检查一下
In my profession，a man is only as good as the car he drives.
男人就得跟他驾驶的车一样棒 这是职业经验
You take care of the car，the car will take care of you.
你照顾好车 车就会照顾好你
The boss says，「Back on the road.」
老板说 「回到路上」
Frank？
Frank啊
Keep at it.
你继续
Back in the car，Frank.
回车里去 Frank
No.
不
Find it？Not yet.
找到了？还没
You're the smart one？
你是机灵的家伙？
No。I'm the big one.
不 我是大家伙
Not so big anymore，are you？
你不再是大家伙了 是吧？
Found it.
找到了
The transmitter。Can you remove it？
发射器 能拆下来么？
It's wired.
有线连著
If I do：it comes boom.
要是我拆了：就爆了
You fight good.
打得很漂亮
But your tie bad.
但领带打很烂
Where are you going？
去哪儿？
Tired.
累了
That's why I prefer to deal with cars.
那就是我更愿意与车相处的原因
That makes two of us.
英雄所见略同
What do you want me to do when they？When they wake up？
他们醒过来之后…？醒了之后 我要怎么办？
Probably best to take the rest of the day off.
或许今天先放个假
I'm not amused.
我很不爽
You'd be less amused if you ended up dead.
要是你不死 你会更不爽
If you wanted me dead，I'd be dead。You need me alive.
如果你想我死 我早就死了 你想让我活著
You want me to complete the job，I need some clarification.
你想要我完成这个任务 我要说明一下
I'm listening.
我在听
In person.
单独听
We've already done in person.
是单独听的
Well，not to my satisfaction，apparently.
噢 显然我不满意
Right now，my satisfaction should be your main concern.
现在 我是否满意是你首要关心的问题
Same place。One hour。Wait for my call.
同一地点 一小时后 等我电话
Hello？
喂？
You've disappointed me.
你让我很失望
You won't be the first and you won't be the last.
你不是第一个 也不会是最后一个
I told you I wanted to do this in person。That won't be necessary。You see…
我告诉过你 我想一个人做这事儿 那没必要 你看…
since our little chat at the beginning
在我们一开始的少许交谈后
I've been thinking I don't need the best for this mundane assignment.
我就一直在想 其实我不需要找最优秀的人来做这种任务
Any idiot with a driver's license will do.
任何持有驾照的白痴都能做到
So in the words of the great American，Donald Trump：
所以 引用伟大的美国人Donald Trump的话：
I'm sorry，but you're fired.
很抱歉 你被解雇了
Who are you？
你是谁？
Your new chauffeur。I want the old one back.
你的新司机 我要旧的那个
He's about to go to pieces.
他就快被炸成肉酱了
You're fired.
你被解雇了
How was your nap？
睡得怎么样？
Restful。How was your phone call？
很安稳 你电话打得怎么了？
Brief。Fasten your seat belt.
简短 系好你的安全带
Tarconi.
Tarconi啊
It's me.
是我
I was wondering when you would call.
我还在想你会什么时候打来呢
I've been busy.
我忙死了
Let me guess。In Budapest？
我来猜猜 在布达佩斯？
You've been busy too.
你也很忙嘛
Never a problem keeping that way with a friend like you，Frank.
用那种方式维系像你这样的朋友关系 不会有问题 Frank
So I don't have to be redundant，tell me what you know.
那好 我就不多说了 告诉我你所知道的
There is a black Mercedes also in Budapest.
布达佩斯有一辆黑色的梅赛德斯
Probably not occupied by friends of yours.
或许并不归你的朋友所有
That is what I know。Now tell me what you know.
我只知道那个 现在告诉我你知道的吧
I have two bags in the back and a girl in the front.
我有两个包在后备箱 一个女孩在前座
Russian，I think.
俄国人 我猜
I don't know what she has to do with anything.
我不知道她跟这一切有什么关系
Have you tried asking her？
你试过问她吗？
Now，why didn't I think of that？Sorry.
为什么我没有想到呢？抱歉
Of course you've asked。And she says？
你当然问过了 那她说什么？
I'm going to die.
我快死了
Typical。Russians.
典型的 俄国人
They are so dark.
他们太抑郁了
I remember，in school，reading Dostoyevsky and thinking
我还记得 在学校时 读著陀思托耶夫斯基 然后想
when do these people laugh？
这些人什么时候才会笑呢？
One page after the other
满满整页都写著
misery and suffering like you wouldn't believe，Frank.
你无法相信的凄酸痛苦 Frank
Inspector，can we save the literature lesson？I'm blinking here.
警长 我们能省掉这节文学课吗？我这儿正闪著呢
Is that code？
那是密码吗？
No，it's some bracelet they accessorized us with.
不是 是他们给我们戴的像手镯一样的东西
Wired to explode if we get too far from the car.
如果我们离车太远 就会爆炸
They？
他们？
Some American.
是些美国人
Can you be more specific？A name？A number？
具体点呢？姓名？号码？
Nothing.
一无所知
Why do you always make it so easy，Frank？
你怎么总是不当回事 Frank？
It's my nature.
天性使然
Where are you？I will come there.
你在哪儿？我去找你
That's not a good idea。They have me on a short leash.
这个想法可不怎么样 我们被看得很紧
I can't be of much help if you do not give me something.
要是你不告诉我点东西 我可帮不上什么忙
How close are you to a computer？
你身边有电脑么？
Yes，Frank？
喂 Frank？
That wasn't very nice，back there in the market.
被扔在市场上 感觉很不好啊
You were the one who broke the rules，not me.
破坏规矩的人是你 不是我
Point well taken.
我承认
That makes us even。What say we start with a clean slate？
我们扯平了 我们重新来过怎么样？
So this call is about kiss-and-make-up，then？
那么这是个握手言和的电话喽？
More or less.
差不多吧
You have what I need to get the bracelet off…
你有去掉我手镯的东西…
I have the packages you need delivered.
而我有你要快递的包裹
Here are the new coordinates，then：2-6-12.
这是新坐标：2-6-12
That'll take you to the place…
那会带你到…
where we can have a conclusion to this business.
此次交易结束的地方
I look forward to it.
我等著你
Frank.
Frank啊
Did you get it？
追踪到了吗？
Got the signal。Give us a little time…
查到了信号 再给我们点时间…
and we should have his number and location.
我们就能破译这个数字还有位置
Your new phone，sir.
你的新手机 先生
Anything else？No.
还有别的事儿吗？没了
Frank，do you know where the signal is taking you？
Frank 你这到这个坐标要带你去哪吗？
I know restaurant there。Fish like you never had.
我知道那儿有家餐厅 那儿的鱼你从没吃过
Roasted with small carrots and black pepper.
跟胡萝卜和黑胡椒一起烘烤
Romanian wine，not so good.
罗马尼亚葡萄酒 倒并不怎么样
But for the last meal，could be worse.
可是作为最后的晚餐 也不算太差
You really should begin to think more positive.
你真该乐观一点儿
I'm realist.
我是个现实主义者
My friend was right when he said you were doom and gloom.
我朋友说你悲观绝望 还真是说对了
What means 「doom and gloom」？
「悲观绝望」是什么意思？
You know，you only see the horrible and the terrible.
你知道的 你只会看到恐惧和害怕
Your friend，where does he get this？He doesn't know me.
你的朋友 他凭什么这么说？他又不认识我
He was talking about you in general。Russians，as a people.
他只是大体上描述了一下 一个俄罗斯人
I'm not Russian。I'm Ukrainian.
我不是俄罗斯人 我是乌克兰人
Excuse me.
抱歉
Not excused。We're different people。We're different here…
不接受 我们是不同的人 我们这儿…
and here.
还有这儿 都不一样
Me，personally，I think there's a little bit of an optimist in you.
我个人觉得 你内心里面也并不完全那么悲观
How you can make such a statement？You don't know me.
这又从何说起？你又不了解我
Well，I see you're putting makeup on.
好啦 我看到你正在化妆打扮
If you were so convinced we was gonna die，why bother？
要是你这么确信我们会死 还这么麻烦干嘛？
What does looking good have to do with dying？
好看跟死有什么关系？
Hello.
咦
What's that？
什么东西？
Souvenirs from Ibiza。Do you want one？
伊比沙岛的特产 你想来一颗吗？
No，thank you。And neither do you。We need to stay sharp.
不 谢了 你也不能吃 我们得保持清醒
Okay.
好吧
You stay sharp.
你保持清醒
I stay，how you say？Optimist？
而我 你怎么说来著？保持乐观？
Give me that。Give me that thing。Give me the pill！
给我 把那东西给我 把药丸给我！
Give me that…
给我…
Jesus.
天
Great.
好极了
Just great。Come on，Frank Martin，lighten up.
真是好极了 别这样 Frank Martin 高兴点儿吧
I should？How about when those pills hit？
我该高兴？药丸起效时怎么办？
You're gonna be lighting up like a goddamn Christmas tree.
你会海得跟个他妈的圣诞树似的
That would be nice.
那也不错啊
Boring。Boring。Boring？
无聊 无聊 无聊？
Oh，yeah.
噢 耶
You should stay in the car.
你该待在车里
You want me to pee in car？
你想我在车里尿尿？
Okay。Go on.
好吧 去吧
You remember.
别忘了
Don't.
不
Oh，no.
噢 不会吧
Stop，all right？Why？I don't drive.
别喝了 行不行？怎么了？我又不开车
I want to have fun.
我只是想开心点儿
I want to be happy。You should try happy instead of so serious.
我想要开心点 你应该试著高兴点 而不是老这么严肃
It's important to stay positive，like you say，yeah？
保持乐观很重要 你说的 不是吗？
Drink with me，Frankie。I don't want a drink.
跟我一起喝吧 Frankie 我不想喝
Now who is all gloomy and doomy？
现在是谁悲观绝望？
I say it right？Gloomy doomy？
我没说错吧？悲观绝望？
Come on，get in the car.
快 上车
I am free，like a bird.
我自由了 像鸟一样自由
The girl！Come on！Faster！
那个女孩！快！开快点！
I have lost my friend！I'll buy you a new one.
我丢了我的朋友！我会再给你买一瓶
Have any idea why we have a car on our ass？
知道为什么有辆车 追在我们屁股后面吗？
I don't know。I don't care.
不知道 我不在乎
You mind？First you say I'm doom and gloom…
不介意小点儿声吧？一开始你说我悲观绝望…
and now you tell me do not be happy？Make up your mind.
而现在你告诉我不要太高兴？别变来变去的
Yes，Frank？I thought we had an agreement.
喂 Frank？我想我们达成了协议
We do.
的确
It had nothing to do with a car on my ass.
跟我身后的那辆车没有任何关系
I don't have anything to do with that。Someone else has issues with you？
我跟那一点关系也没有 是不是跟你有恩怨的人？
Likely.
可能吧
What I think is that there are other forces at work here.
我想是有其他势力在办事
Let me check into it，see what I can find out.
让我查一下 看看能不能找到什么
What do I do in the meantime？
那我现在要怎么做？
Drive faster.
开快点吧
What the hell is he doing？
他妈的他在干什么？
There！
那儿！
He's down there！
他在那儿！
I'm hungry.
我饿啦
Should have thought about a sandwich，not vodka.
早该想到买块三明治 而不是伏特加
Look！
那儿！
I wasn't hungry then，I was thirsty.
那会儿我不是饿 是渴
Why you are so mean to me？
你为什么要那样针对我？
- I'm not being mean。I'm preoccupied。- What means 「preoccupied」？
- 我不是针对 我才没这个心思 - 「没心思」是什么意思？
That means preoccupied.
这就是没心思
Shoot the tires！Come on！Get him！
射轮胎！快！抓住他！
Get down！Shoot him！
趴下！射他！
Bloody hell！
搞什么飞机！
Faster！
开快点！
Stop the car！
快停车！
Oh，shit！
噢 挂了！
What are you doing？
你在干嘛？
You're so tense.
你太紧张了
You don't say.
用不著你来说
I make you relax，okay？
我来给你放松放松 如何？
Yeah。I'm good at this.
好吧 我很在行
Making tense go away.
消除紧张
What are you doing？
你干嘛呢？
I want to feel sex one more time before I die.
我想在死之前 再一次感受性爱
Don't you？
难道你不想吗？
What is it with you and dying？
那跟你还有死 有什么关系？
There is something wrong with me？
我有什么问题吗？
Am I not sexy？
难道我不够性感？
Yeah，you're sexy.
不是 你很性感
You're the gay.
噢 你是同志
Nope，I am not the gay.
不 我不是同志
I don't mind.
我不介意的
I'm not，okay？
我不是 好不好？
Then what's the problem？
那还有什么问题？
Did it ever occur to you that maybe I'm not in the mood？
你有没有想到过 可能是我没心情？
I thought rule is don't open package。It is.
我以为规则是 不能打开包裹 没错
Why you have rules if you break them？
如果破坏了规矩 还要它干嘛？
I keep asking myself the same thing.
我也一直这样问我自己
Phone books.
电话薄
You're the package。Yes.
你才是那个包裹 没错
Could have said something.
为什么不早说
Would it make a difference？Yes.
有什么区别么？有
Now what are you doing？
你要干嘛？
You know，back in garage…
你知道的 在停车场…
it was very turn-on to me when you take off your clothes.
你脱掉衣服的时候 真是让人兴奋
I was trying to keep five cretins from caving my head in.
我当时正竭力不让那五个白痴抓住我们
I don't see the turn-on in that.
我可不觉得有什么好兴奋的
You think it's only man gets turned on by striptease？
你以为 只有男人才会被脱衣舞勾起欲望？
I don't like where this is going，Valentina.
我可不喜欢事情变成这样 Valentina
Would you striptease for me again？
你能为我再脱一次吗？
Give me the keys。This is not funny.
给我钥匙 这并不好玩
You want keys？
想要钥匙？
I want you to stop playing around，is what I want.
别闹了 这才是我想要的
Maybe it's last chance to play around for you and for me.
也许这是你我最后一次好好玩的机会了
This is not the time or the place for playing.
这不是玩的地方 现在也不是玩的时候
Why do I get feeling with you it's never time or place？
那为什么我会在此时此刻 对你有感觉呢？
If I wanna get analyzed，I'll see a psychiatrist.
如果我需要分析 我会去找心理医生
Now，give me the keys.
快 把钥匙给我
Come on，Frank Martin.
来吧 Frank Martin
Make playtime for me.
一起玩吧
All right？That enough？
行了吧？够不够？
Not enough。That is not a striptease，Frank.
不够 那不叫脱衣舞 Frank
Striptease is sexy。You know，move your ass a little.
脱衣舞得性感 你知道的 扭扭屁股
Come on，Frank Martin.
来吧 Frank Martin
You want keys？
你想要钥匙？
I want strip.
我想要脱衣舞
You know what I'm gonna do to you for making me do this？
让我做这些 你知道会有什么后果么？
Spank me？
打我？
For starters.
只是开始
Tie me up？You'd like that，wouldn't you？
把我绑起来？你会喜欢的 不是吗？
I like the rough stuff.
我喜欢粗暴型的
Really？
真的吗？
Oh，but not too rough.
哦 但别太粗暴了
Deal was a striptease for the keys.
交易是脱衣舞换钥匙
New deal。Kiss me for the keys.
新交易 吻我 我就给你钥匙
Like you mean it.
用点儿心
Do you ever kiss like you mean it，Frank？
你有真心吻过一个人么 Frank？
I'm thinking maybe not.
我想也许没有
I'm thinking you live alone.
我猜 你是一个人住的
Inside and outside.
不论在家还是在外
Thinking it is not dying you're afraid of.
我想 你并不惧怕死亡
It's living.
而是惧怕生活
Live with me.
跟我一起生活吧
Just this once.
就这一次
Just this moment。Live with me.
就这会儿 跟我一起生活
What's his position？We lost him.
他的位置在哪？我们跟丢了
He headed into the mountains。We can't get reception up there.
他进了山区 我们接收不到那里的信号
Hack into one of the military satellites.
侵入军用卫星
Yes.
是我
You think we're playing games here，Mr Minister？
你觉得我们是在玩游戏吗 部长先生？
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
I'm talking about a black car full of your incompetent operatives.
我在说一辆载著你无能手下的黑色轿车
One more move like that and you will never see your daughter again.
再有这样的动作 你就再也别想见到你女儿
I want to hear her voice.
我想听听她的声音
When the contract is signed and delivered.
等合约签好传过来之后吧
I will not sign until I hear her voice.
听不到她的声音 我是不会签的
You are in no position to play hardball，Mr Minister.
你没有强硬的资格 部长先生
Well，neither are you，Mr Johnson.
那好 你也没有 Johnson先生
Yes，I know who you are.
没错 我知道你是谁
And I can assure you，if anything happens to my daughter…
我敢保证 如果我女儿有什么闪失…
I will use all the power I have.
我会动用我所有的权力
I will hunt you down and make you pay in a most hideous way for this.
抓住你 让你用最可怕的方式来偿还
We have to move now.
开始行动
Pick up，Frank。Pick up.
接啊 Frank 快接
I'm in Ibiza。Making holiday.
我正在伊比沙岛 度假
Someone hands me glass of champagne.
有人递给我一杯香槟
I drink.
我喝了
Then I don't feel so good.
然后觉得有点儿不舒服
I go to bathroom，and next thing，I'm awake in the car.
我去了洗手间 之后的事儿我就不知道了 等我醒来时 就在这车上了
I ask him，「Where is this？」 He tells me he's just a transporter.
我问他：「这是哪儿？」 他说他只是个送货的
He's pretty good driver.
他的车开得很棒
Not like you good.
当然 没有你棒
I tell him，「Please。My father a really powerful man.
我告诉他：「求你了 我父亲是个有权有势的人
Big influence。Knows a lot of people。Let me call him.「
很有影响力 认识很多人 让我给他打个电话吧「
He's afraid。He's never done this before.
他很害怕 他以前从没这样做过
It's supposed to be simple。Pick up，drop off。Easy money.
本来应该很简单的 载人 离开 来钱很容易
He's been told no calls，never leave car.
有人告诉他 不能打电话 不能离开车
But I convince him.
但我说服了他
I call.
我打了电话
But before I say to my father where we are…
但我还没来得及跟父亲说上话…
Inside the car。Come on！
上车 快！
We get away，but…
我们逃走了 但…
There's people shooting at us。Why？
有人朝我们开枪 为什么？
Why they shooting at us？
他们为什么要杀我们呢？
He says they shoot because we didn't go according to plan.
他说他们开枪 是因为我们没有遵造计划
I said，「Okay，that's the old plan。What's new plan？」
我说 「好吧 那是旧计划 新的计划呢？」
He says he has a friend.
他说他有一个朋友
And then I met you.
之后我就遇到了你
And then I feel it's gonna be okay.
见到你 我就觉得安全了
You didn't even know me.
你甚至都不认识我
Of course I don't know you.
我当然不认识你
I talk about feelings，not knowing.
我说的是感觉 不是认不认识
Well，if you was feeling that way，you sure had a funny way of showing it.
如果你有那种感觉 你表达的方式真是有趣
Better for a woman to have a little mystery to her.
对女人来说 有一点神秘感会更好
No？
不是吗？
No.
不是
Yes。Just a little.
是的 只是一点点
He's back on the radar，sir.
他回到雷达监控上了 先生
Yeah。Where the hell are you？
喂 你他妈到底在哪？
On the way to Bucharest.
在去布加勒斯特的路上
Not any longer.
地点换了
New coordinates：3-7-13.
新坐标：3-7-13
Excuse me，Mr。Minister.
打扰一下 部长先生
Sorry，just a minute.
抱歉 请稍等
Inspector Tarconi，from Marseilles.
我是警长Tarconi 来自马赛
Well，not exactly Marseilles…
说马赛也不是很准确…
but a small town to the east What do you want，inspector？
是马赛东边的一个小镇 你想做什么呢 警长？
A word with you。I have no time.
和您谈谈 我没时间
It's about your daughter.
跟您的女儿有关
Odessa，Frank。My country.
敖德萨 Frank 我的故乡
You take me home。Thank you.
你带我回家了 谢谢你
What happened to Bucharest？
怎么不去布加勒斯特了？
Change of plans。It's a good change。I prefer Odessa.
计划有变 变得好 我更喜欢敖德萨
Yeah.
是嘛
I was looking forward to that fish with the carrots myself.
我倒是期待著鱼和胡萝卜呢
Oh，it's much better here.
哦 这儿的食物更美味
You know chicken Kiev？I do.
你知道基辅鸡吗？当然
I know restaurant here.
我知道这儿的一家餐厅
Best in the world.
是世界上最棒的
The chicken's so fresh。And the butter，when it's coming out…
鸡肉鲜美 还有黄油 当它溢出来时…
Like you cannot believe，it's so nice.
你肯定不敢相信 会有多美味
You know what I feel like now？
你知道我现在是什么感觉吗？
Hungry.
饿了？
Safe.
感觉安全
It's going to end up like the movies，this happily ever after？
这会像电影的结局那样吗 从此过著幸福快乐的生活？
By tonight，this is all gonna be a fading memory.
今晚 这一切都将成为褪色的回忆
It's gonna be you and me，laughing over chicken Kiev.
你跟我微笑著坐在基辅鸡店里
Liar.
骗子
Mr。Minister，an update，please.
部长先生 决定做好了吧
I am ready to sign the contract once I speak to my daughter.
我准备好了 一旦跟我女儿通过话 就可以签合同
Hello？Hello？
喂？喂？
Have that pen ready。I'll call you back.
把笔准备好 一会儿打给你
Yeah。We are closing the noose，Frank.
喂 我们要收网了 Frank
Well，when it closes，make sure no one tries to drag me out of the car.
好吧 收网的时候 确保没人来把我拖下车
You know what this is about yet？
你现在知道这是怎么回事了吗？
The girl。Her father.
那个女孩 她父亲
Large amounts of toxic waste.
和大量的有毒废料
It is a trade。His signature for her life.
这是一场交易 他的签名换她的命
I have a reputation to uphold here，inspector.
我有我的信誉 警长
One hundred percent successful delivery rate.
完成送货任务率是百分之百
Am I detecting a little attachment？
我好像听出来点儿什么苗头？
That is not the Frank I know。With his rules，no names，no attachment.
那不是我所认识的Frank 他的规则是 不问姓名 不牵涉感情
Why is everyone so concerned about my rules？
为什么每个人都对我的规则那么感兴趣？
Frank，I always suspected you are a romantic at heart.
Frank 我一直认为 其实你的内心是浪漫的
Anything else？
还有别的事儿吗？
Where is the rendezvous？
目的地在哪儿？
I'll call you back.
我再打给你
Yeah。We're almost at the end，Frank.
喂 快结束了 Frank
Just give me the coordinates。No more coordinates.
把坐标给我 没有坐标了
The road you're on.
就在你现在那条路上
Make your first left.
第一个路口左拐
I'd like to know where I'm going.
我想知道我要去哪儿
You'll know when you get there.
到了你就知道了
Don't worry。We got them right where we want them.
不要担心 这地方正是我想带他们来的
My compliments，Frank.
我很欣赏你 Frank
Our trust in your abilities was well deserved.
你的能力果然值得我们信任
Now if you could please send the girl out.
现在你可以让那女孩出来了
She's coming.
她马上出去
I'm not coming.
我不走
They need you。They won't kill you.
他们需要你 他们不会杀你的
But they will kill you.
但他们会杀你
Do I look like a man who came halfway across Europe to die on a bridge？
难道我看上去像那种穿越半个欧洲 然后死在桥上的人吗？
Do I？
我像吗？
We don't have all day，Frank.
我们可没有这么多耐心 Frank
Look how many of them.
他们有那么多人
They have all the guns.
他们都有枪
How it's gonna be okay？
怎么会没事呢？
Tell you over dinner.
晚饭的时候告诉你
Now，go.
现在 走吧
Go.
走啊
Kiss me.
吻我
Go.
去吧
You're gonna get me killed。Now，go.
你会害死我的 快 出去
Get to her，you bastard.
抓她啊 混蛋
Better now，darling？
亲爱的 好点了吗？
Finish him.
干掉他
No！Frank！
不！Frank！
His beloved car will be his grave.
他的爱车将成为他的坟墓
Leaves it，he blows。Stays，he drowns。Let's get out of here.
爬出来 他会被炸死 留里面 他会被淹死 我们撤吧
Tarconi。They have the girl.
Tarconi 女孩在他们手上
Frank，we are trying to track him through the phone signal.
Frank 我们试著从手机信号追踪他
Where are you？In a lake.
你在哪儿？湖里
A lake？
湖？
Can you be more specific？
你能具体点吗？
There's a dam.
这有个水坝
A dam？I know the place，sir.
水坝？我知道那个地方 长官
How far？Ten minutes at least.
多远？至少要十分钟
Frank，we'll be there in 10 minutes.
Frank 我们十分钟左右到
Can you make it any faster？
能快点儿吗？
We'll do our best。Thank you.
我们会尽力的 谢谢
Buy tickets for all of us.
把全部人的票都买了
Where to？
去哪儿？
Anywhere this train is going。We need to keep moving for half an hour.
不管这车去哪儿 我们得继续走半个小时
Why don't we just keep driving around？
为什么我们不继续开车走呢？
Another day.
改日再算
Sir！There！
长官！那儿！
Out。Out！Everybody out！
出去 出去！所有人都出去！
Come on。Move！
快 滚！
Move，quick！
出去 快点！
Mr。Minister？Yes.
部长先生？是的
Someone wants to talk to you.
有人想跟你谈谈
Papa。Are you all right？
爸爸 你还好吗？
Don't sign.
不要签
What you have is 15 minutes.
你还有15分钟
You ever find out what this is about？Garbage.
你有没有查出这究竟是怎么回事？废料
How much garbage are we talking？
我们谈的是多少废料呢？
Enough to pollute half the country for a hundred years.
足够污染半个国家一百年的废料
Try it again.
再试一次
For a modern woman，you are very uninformed.
作为一个现代女性 你是相当的无知
This is the new world.
这是个新世界
There are no more countries。That's old think.
不再有国家 那是旧的观念
There are just economic realities。Profit and loss.
只有现实的经济利益 赢利和亏损
Efficiency and waste.
效率和浪费
Think global，not local.
放眼全球 不再有地域之分
Think this.
去你妈的
Yes？Where are we？
喂？进展如何？
We're almost there.
快完成了
Where？
在哪？
Here。He is on a train.
这儿 他在火车上
And where are we？Here.
我们在哪儿？这儿
We can get units there.
我们可以在那儿跟火车接上头
That's a good idea。Do that.
这个主意不错 就这么办
Oh，Frank，come on.
哦 Frank 拜托
Mr。Minister，I assure you，everything is in order.
部长先生 我向您保证 一切尽在掌握之中
I'm sure it is.
我相信是的
If there are any problems I know you will solve them.
如果有什么问题 我知道你们会解决的
Now，if you don't mind…
现在 请先出去吧…
You might not believe this，but I am，at heart，a pacifist.
你可能不信 但在我内心里 我是一个和平主义者
I hate violence.
我讨厌暴力
It creates more problems than it solves.
暴力造成的问题比能解决的要多
You know，I never wanted to do any of this.
现在的一切 也并不是我所愿意的
A client asked me to obtain a result…
客户提出了要求…
so I went about creating an environment…
但我想用最少的血…
with the least amount of bloodshed.
来达到他的要求
No one wanted to cooperate。Not you，not the first driver…
可是没有人愿意合作 你不想 第一个司机不想…
not your father，not the recently deceased Frank Martin.
你父亲不想 刚死掉的Frank Martin也不想
Everyone wanted to fight.
每个人都想反抗
What's so funny？
有什么好笑的？
Hearing a dead man talking.
听一个死人说话
One more step，Frank.
再走走试试啊 Frank
Come on。One more.
来吧 再走走
Look.
看
It's over.
已经结束了
Two minutes to 9。He signed.
8：58 他签了
Oh，my God.
哦 天呐
No，Frank。No，no.
不要 Frank 不 不要
It's over，Frank。It's over.
结束了 Frank 结束了
Mission accomplished。You and the girl are free to go.
任务完成了 你和那女孩可以走了
Matter of fact，I'm so impressed by your talent…
事实上 你的能力让我印象深刻…
I'd like to offer you a position.
我可以给你提供一份职位
I'd like to offer you one。Permanently disabled.
我也想给你提供一份 永远残废
I hate to waste talent.
我讨厌浪费人材
But I really don't think we'd make a very good fit.
但我真的不觉得我们合得来
That's right.
没错
No！
不要！
We wouldn't fit，but you and the bracelet were made for each other.
我们是不合适 但你和手镯炸弹是天生一对
No，no.
不 不要
No！
不！
不要！
You're doing the right thing.
你是在做正确的事
Valentina.
Valentina啊
Am I in heaven？
我上天堂了吗？
Looks more like we're in hell.
看起来更像是地狱
I don't care.
我不在乎
As long as we're there together.
只要我们在一起
Yes？
喂？
Mr。Minister，your daughter is in good hands.
部长先生 您女儿在我们这儿
Thank you.
谢谢你
What are you doing？What you said，the right thing.
你在做什么？如你所说 做正确的事
And now，gentlemen。if you'll excuse me，I have a conference to address…
现在 先生们 失陪 我去要开会了…
on the dangers of doing business with people like you.
在会上我会说 跟你这样的人做生意是很危险的
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Is the launch ready？
逃生艇下水了吗？
It's on the water，sir，waiting。Time to leave.
在水上了 先生 等著呢 快逃吧
- Grab the log。- Okay.
- 带上航海日志 - 好
I just don't understand it.
我只是不明白
When I was a boy，my father and I…
小时候 我爸和我…
used to pull fish out of this very spot all day long.
总是能从这儿钓上来鱼
Times change，inspector.
时代变了 警长
As do people.
人也一样
You referring to me？
你是说我？
I don't think that's a very accurate statement.
我不认为这个言论很准确
I drive the same car，live in the same house.
我开著原来的车 住在原来的房子里
Oh，I was not referring to your car or your house.
哦 我不是指你的车或是房子
The sea is so restful.
大海真是宁静啊
Is lunch ready yet？
午餐准备好了吗？
Mademoiselle，there is a certain progression to things.
小姐 事物发展是有先后的
In order to eat the lunch，you first have to catch the lunch.
要吃午餐 得先钓到鱼
And if we keep talking instead of concentrating…
如果我们继续闲聊 还不集中精神的话…
we're gonna catch nothing.
我们什么都钓不到
I have better idea。Why we don't skip catching of lunch…
我有个更好的主意 为什么我们不跳过抓鱼这步…
and go right to eating of lunch？
直接去吃午餐呢？
I know wonderful place just up coast from here…
我知道离这不远 有个很棒的地方…
where they make fish stew。Incredible.
他们焖的鱼 超级美味
They use tomatoes and onions，and little amount of wild lavender.
用番茄和洋葱 撒上少量的野生薰衣草
What kind of wine？
配什么酒呢？
Pink。From south.
桃红的葡萄酒 南方货
A Chateauneuf，perhaps.
可能还是城堡里储藏的哦
- Chilled。- Of course，chilled.
- 要加冰 - 当然要加冰
And for dessert？
甜点呢？